A Guide to the Russell Gregg Photograph Collection, ca. 1920-1944
Thomas Balch Library
- (Digital)
  - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team], 1940
  - [Lincoln High School], 1940
  - [Lincoln High School], 1940
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1940
  - [Miss Myers - graduation], 1940
  - [Moyer baby], 1940
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1940
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1940
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1940
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1940
  - [Round Hill School], 1940
  - [nichols store fire, exterior], 1940
  - [nichols store fire, exterior], 1940
  - [nichols store fire, interior], 1940
  - [Purcellville library - Grandfather Clock], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - auto parts shelves], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - chairs and desks], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - fireplace], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - landscaping], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - meeting room], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - meeting room], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - outside building], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - Old Meeting House, Marian Holcombe], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - patio], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - reading area], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - stacks], 1940 ca.
  - [Purcellville library - unidentified woman], 1940 ca.
  - [Ball Wedding], 1941
  - [Ball Wedding], 1941
  - [Ball Wedding], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Douglass High School], 1941
  - [Farmhill School students], 1941
  - [Girl Scouts], 1941
  - [Leesburg High School Football Team], 1941
  - [Leesburg High School Football Team], 1941
  - [Leesburg High School Football Team], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln High School], 1941
  - [Lincoln School], 1941
  - [Lincoln School], 1941
  - [Lucketts Elementary School], 1941
  - [Lucketts Elementary School], 1941
  - [Lucketts Elementary School], 1941
  - [Purcellville elementary school - music class], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School], 1941
  - [Round Hill High School], 1941
  - [Aldie High School Boys Basket Ball], 1942
  - [Aldie High School Girls Basketball], 1942
  - [Aldie High School Teachers], 1942
  - [Aldie High School], 1942
  - [Aldie High School], 1942
  - [Aldie High School], 1942
  - [Aldie High School], 1942
  - [Leesburg High School], 1942
  - [Lincoln High School Basketball Team], 1942
  - [Lincoln High School Football Team], 1942
  - [Lincoln High School], 1942
  - [Lincoln High School], 1942
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1942
  - [Purcellville School WWII Tire Drive], 1942
  - [Aldie High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lincoln High School], 1943
  - [Lovettsville High School Teachers], 1943
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1943
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1943
  - [Aldie High School Basketball], 1944
  - [Aldie High School Basketball], 1944
  - [Aldie High School], 1944
  - [Aldie High School], 1944
  - [Aldie High School], 1944
  - [Aldie High School], 1944
  - [Aldie School], 1944
  - [Arthur Elgin], 1944
  - [Frank Legard], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Basketball Team], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Basketball Team], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School], 1944
  - [Leesburg High School], 1944
  - [Lincoln High School Baseball Team], 1944
  - [Lincoln High School Basketball Team], 1944
  - [Lincoln High School F.A.A.], 1944
  - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team], 1944
  - [Lincoln High School], 1944
  - [Lovettsville High School Teachers], 1944
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1944
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1944
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1944
  - [Lovettsville High School], 1944
  - [Hamilton Elementary School Students], 1936
  - [Everhart Family], 1910
  - [Round Hill School], 1920
  - [St. Pauls Episcopal Church]
  - [Baptist Church]
  - [Purcellville, VA]
  - [Purcellville Business Section]
  - [Purcellville, VA]
  - [Purcellville, VA]
  - [Looking west from the Water Tower on a clear morning]
  - [Joe Lacey], 1936
  - [Hamilton School], 1934
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lucketts School Baseball Team], 1933
  - [Lucketts School], 1933
  - [Lincoln School], 1934 ca.
  - [Lincoln School Football Team], 1934 ca.
  - [Lincoln School Graduates], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Students], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Students], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Students], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Students], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Band], 1935
  - [Lincoln School], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Football Team], 1935
  - [Lincoln School Graduates], 1935
  - [Lincoln School], 1936
  - [Lincoln School Baseball Team], 1936
  - [Lincoln School Basketball Team], 1936
  - [Leesburg School Basketball], 1944
  - [Leesburg School Basketball], 1939
  - [Leesburg School Football], 1939